<ModOps>

 <!-- Asset List -->

  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
		
		<!--Items-->

		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119190</GUID>
			<Text>Bonny and Clyde</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119170</GUID>
			<Text>The most notorious gangsters in the entire kingdom. Cruel and unscrupulous, but at the same time admired and cheered by the people.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119191</GUID>
			<Text>Cornelius "Commodore" Vanderbilt</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119171</GUID>
			<Text>Tycoon, multi-billionaire and ruthless monopoly. But nobody builds a railroad faster.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119192</GUID>
			<Text>Charles Lloyd Rockateller</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119172</GUID>
			<Text>Planning a skyscraper that will even surpass Donny Bader's SkyTower - completely made of wood.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119193</GUID>
			<Text>Prof. Linus Liquiscious</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119173</GUID>
			<Text>Dean of the Faculty of Chemistry. Runs a thriving black market with all kinds of homemade spirits in his laboratory.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119194</GUID>
			<Text>Dewey Hasselbay, the Human Amphibian</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119174</GUID>
			<Text>Tanned, muscular and always to be found with a smile when he's not underwater again.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119195</GUID>
			<Text>Frank Stone, the Butcher</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119175</GUID>
			<Text>There ... a noticeably high ... employee turnover in your butcher's shop was found. Certainly just the high workload ...</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119196</GUID>
			<Text>Priscilla Lovetroy, Prominent Friend of Donny Bader</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119176</GUID>
			<Text>Starting in the dusty saloons of the Wild West, today she is a beguiling actress and dancer who lets the worries of the big city dwellers be forgotten in no time.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119197</GUID>
			<Text>W. H. Twain, the First Gold Digger</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119177</GUID>
			<Text>Leaving home decades ago, always looking for big money, he was the first to discover the sheer riches deep in the ground just waiting to be discovered. Routinely and with a keen eye, he goes about his work and brings to light everything that shines.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119198</GUID>
			<Text>Sir Abraham Woolsworth, Vulcanist of the Empire</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119178</GUID>
			<Text>Knighted for the development of new rubber production processes. He comes from the bottom up and has suffered numerous setbacks. But he knows how to save scarce resources.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119199</GUID>
			<Text>Tuvalu Mbesa, the Special Pipe Maker</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119179</GUID>
			<Text>Unobtrusively sows poppy seeds under his aunt's hibiscus fields and uses them to make pipes and cigars that are particularly popular overseas.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119200</GUID>
			<Text>TorpedoProjectile_D</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119201</GUID>
			<Text>Ironbrights Defender of Freedom</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119181</GUID>
			<Text>Designed to quickly, quietly and efficiently deal large area damage to the enemy. It achieves its enormous destructive power through four explosive devices built into the fuselage.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119202</GUID>
			<Text>Blackbeard's Captain flag</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119182</GUID>
			<Text>With the flag of the dreaded pirate Blackbeard, you evoke fear and horror from a great distance. </Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119203</GUID>
			<Text>Wang Mingzuo, Guardian of the Fortune Cookies</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119183</GUID>
			<Text>What is it? A biscuit with a wise saying inside? Oh how delightful!</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119204</GUID>
			<Text>Lord Coulter McBain, Conqueror of the Arctic</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119184</GUID>
			<Text>An old companion of John Franklin. After his tragic expedition through the Arctic, he settled there to master the icy climes in John's honor.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119205</GUID>
			<Text>Dakota Earp, King of the Cattle Trails</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119185</GUID>
			<Text>No matter how big the herd, no matter how stubborn and unruly: He drives them stoically across the continent and effortlessly catches every runaway.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119206</GUID>
			<Text>James Carson Hickock, Crown Bay Company Marshal Commissioner</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119207</GUID>
			<Text>Crown Bay Reward Pool</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119186</GUID>
			<Text>Controls ships and ports very purposefully and efficiently and finds every contraband, no matter how well hidden.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119208</GUID>
			<Text>Makataime "Black Eagle" Shekiakiak, Cultivator of Ancient Species</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119188</GUID>
			<Text>Spends most of the day in the fields, but nobody knows exactly what he is doing there. Some say there is a ghostly, yet at the same time engaging, peaceful aura about him.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119209</GUID>
			<Text>Saint of the Death</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119189</GUID>
			<Text>Experimental automatic firearm that does not give the enemy time to react.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119169</GUID>
			<Text>Omar Al Zahir, Passionate Storyteller</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119149</GUID>
			<Text>A descendant of the powerful Grand Vizier Ibn Hakim and a good friend of Emperor Ketema. Hardly anyone can escape the spell of his captivating stories from 1001 nights.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119168</GUID>
			<Text>Montgomery Lincoln, Founder of the Panamerican Gentlemen Club</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119148</GUID>
			<Text>Moved to the south many years ago, he established an extremely coveted old men's club in the seedy basement rooms of the boxing arenas, which leaves nothing to be desired. Legal? Nobody cares!</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119167</GUID>
			<Text>Tatsumi Yamazaki, Scholar from the Far East</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119147</GUID>
			<Text>Maintain calm and serenity in every situation and thus contribute significantly to peace on the campus. The dean furthermore noticed the scholars' communication skills have noticeably improved.</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119153</GUID>
			<Text>Item Rerun Trigger</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119160</GUID>
			<Text>BackpackersSpecialistsGuildhouse</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119161</GUID>
			<Text>BackpackersConsumables</Text>
		</Text>
		<Text>
			<!-- TODO translation -->
			<GUID>2100119162</GUID>
			<Text>BackpackersSpecialistsTownhall</Text>
		</Text>
				
  </ModOp>

</ModOps>